Planned Parenthood Federation of America Records (PPFA II): SERIES II. CLASSIFIED FILES, 1921-80 (Part 2)
Sophia Smith Collection
- SERIES II. CLASSIFIED FILES (part 2)
  - I & E Department
    - Films
      - Sex & Responsibility (Goldman), 1969-70 (Box 63, Folder 26)
      - Suffolk County Film, 1969-71 (Box 63, Folder 27)
      - Vision Associates "The Day Before Tomorrow," 1969-72 (Box 63, Folder 28)
    - Fund Raising
      - Campaign kit, 1977-78 (Box 63, Folder 29-30)
      - Publicity Items, 1975-76 (Box 63, Folder 31-32)
      - Annual Publicity/Fund Raising Materials, 1973-74 (Box 63, Folder 33)
      - Materials & Questionnaire, 1973-74 (Box 63, Folder 34)
      - Campaigns
        - 1973 (Box 63, Folder 35)
        - Create-Your-Own-Package, 1973, n.d. (Box 63, Folder 36)
        - Materials, 1971-72 (Box 63, Folder 37)
        - Sales to PPWP Affiliates, 1971 (Box 63, Folder 38)
        - Report, 1969-71 (Box 63, Folder 39)
        - Materials, 1970 (Box 63, Folder 40)
        - Dept. Correspondence, 1969-72 (Box 63, Folder 41)
        - Mother's Day Campaign, circa 1975 (Box 63, Folder 42)
        - Questionnaire, 1970-71 (Box 63, Folder 43)
      - Radio & TV, 1972 (Box 63, Folder 44)
    - Misc., General Correspondence, 1970-74 (Box 63, Folder 45)
    - Committee Correspondence, 1959-63 (Box 63, Folder 46)
    - General Correspondence, 1964-69 (Box 63, Folder 47-48)
    - Institute for Study of Health & Society, 1970 (Box 63, Folder 49)
    - IPPF, 1970 (Box 63, Folder 50)
    - International Women's Year
      - 1974 (Box 63, Folder 51)
      - 1975 (Box 63)
    - Job Description
      - Consultant on Public Affairs, 1973 (Box 63, Folder 52)
      - 1970 (Box 63, Folder 53)
    - National
      - Comics, "Escape from Fear", Correspondence, 1957-67 (Box 63, Folder 54)
      - Contraception, "Memo to Nurses" Manual, Correspondence, 1959-66 (Box 63, Folder 55)
    - Dhew Publications Contract, Memos & General Correspondence, 1974 (Box 63, Folder 56)
    - Guide for Ordering Publications, 1976 (Box 63, Folder 57)
    - Literature
      - Distribution Reports, 1956-72 (Box 63, Folder 58)
      - "Free Under Mott Plan," 1965-67 (Box 63, Folder 59)
      - General Correspondence, 1961-73 (Box 63, Folder 60-61)
    - World Population Year, 1974 (Box 63, Folder 62)
    - Sources for VD Literature, circa 1973 (Box 63, Folder 63)
    - Publications
      - ABC'S of Birth Control, 1970 (Box 63, Folder 64)
      - Abortion Guide, 1970-71 (Box 63, Folder 65)
      - The Future Is Now, 1970 (Box 63, Folder 66)
      - Public Information, PP Guide to Birth Control Legal (Paul, Eve), 1978 (Box 63, Folder 67)
      - Memos
        - 1969-74 (Box 63, Folder 68)
        - 1977 (Box 63)
      - Plans, 1974 (Box 63, Folder 69)
    - National, Literature Requests
      - Directory of Family Planning, 1964 (n.d. - empty folder) (Box 63, Folder 70)
      - Spanish Language Groups, 1962-71 (Box 63, Folder 71)
      - Mimeos, 1957-64 (Box 63, Folder 72)
    - Publications
      - Questionnaire, General, 1973 (Box 64, Folder 1)
      - Review of Spanish PPWP Publications, 1971 (Box 64, Folder 2)
      - Voluntary Sterilization for Men & Women, 1970-71 (Box 64, Folder 3)
      - Status Report, 1973 (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - Mass Media Materials, 1969 (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - Material & Information Exchange, 1973 (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - Motivational research, 1970 (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - Patient Recruitment Campaign, Correspondence, 1969-70 (Box 64, Folder 8)
    - PP in Action, A Who-Does-What, 1972 (Box 64, Folder 9)
    - Public Information, PP News, Memos and Correspondence, 1977-79 (Box 64, Folder 10)
    - Misc. Staff Permission to Reprint
      - 1970-74 (Box 64, Folder 11)
      - 1975-77 (Box 64)
    - PP Report (Formerly PP News), 1968-70 (Box 64, Folder 12)
    - Press Release, Correspondence, 1969 (Box 64, Folder 13)
    - Public Relations Action Tips, 1974 (Box 64, Folder 14)
    - Questionnaires, 1969 (Box 64, Folder 15)
    - Requests for Proposals, Dhew
      - 1974 (Box 64, Folder 16)
      - 1975-78 (Box 64)
    - RFP-HSA 240-BCHS-195 (5) Recipient Koba Associates, Abstract & Final Report, 1975 (Box 64, Folder 17)
    - Sanger Biography Project, 1970 (Box 64, Folder 18)
    - Sex Education, 1968-69 (Box 64, Folder 19)
    - Six Tough Questions Facts, Tips, Etc., circa 1975, CLOSED[no folders 21-25] (Box 64, Folder 20)
    - National, Slides, 1955-70 (Box 64, Folder 26)
    - Speakers' Bureau, 1974 (Box 64, Folder 27)
    - Spreading the Word, 1970-72 (Box 64, Folder 28)
    - Status Report, Major Projects & Activities, 1970 (Box 64, Folder 29)
    - Students, Correspondence, 1970 (Box 64, Folder 30)
    - Ted Bates & Co., 1969-70 (Box 64, Folder 31)
    - Planned Parenthood in Action, A Who-Does-What, 1972 (Box 64, Folder 32)
    - Population Education
      - John Scanlan, 1970-71 (Box 64, Folder 33)
      - Preliminary Plan, 1970 (Box 64, Folder 34)
      - Advisory Group on Pop. Ed. Report to Exp. & Policy & Board February, 1968 (Box 64, Folder 35)
    - Report to LBJ, FP & Pop ED, 1968-69 (Box 64, Folder 36)
    - Projects, 1970 (Box 64, Folder 37)
    - Public Affairs
      - 1973-74 (Box 64, Folder 38)
      - Draft for Manual, circa 1976 (Box 64, Folder 39)
      - Communication Memos, 1980 (Box 64, Folder 40)
    - Radio/TV
      - 1969-70 (Box 64, Folder 41)
      - Directory of Broadcast Spots, 1976 (Box 64, Folder 42)
      - Nab Code Authority Contraceptive Ban, 1976-78 (Box 64, Folder 43)
    - TV
      - 1969-74 (Box 64, Folder 44)
      - 1975-76 (Box 64)
      - Federal Communications Commission, 1973 (Box 64, Folder 45)
      - CBS, "Maude's Dilemma," 1972-74 (Box 64, Folder 46)
      - Fairness Doctrine (FCC)
        - 1974 (Box 64, Folder 47)
        - 1975-80 (Box 64)
      - Memos, General
        - 1970-74 (Box 64, Folder 48)
        - 1975-77 (Box 64)
      - Net Projects, 1970-71 (Box 64, Folder 49)
      - Spots for Patient Recruitment, 1968-69 (Box 64, Folder 50)
    - STAFF
      - Public Information, Barker, Mimi, PR Coordinator, 1978 (Box 64, Folder 51)
      - I & E Dept, Blair, Bee, Consultant, Abortion, 6/15/1973-8/9/1973 (Box 64, Folder 52)
    - ROBIN ELLIOT
      - Public Information, Elliot, Robin
        - Articles, Papers, 2/25/1978-4/11/1978 (Box 64, Folder 53)
        - Correspondence & Memos, 10/6/1978-3/20/1979 (Box 64, Folder 54)
      - I & E Department, Elliot, Robin
        - Correspondence & Memos, 1977 (Box 64, Folder 55)
        - Correspondence and Memos
          - 1971-1974 (Box 64, Folder 56)
          - 1975-1976 (Box 64)
        - Ethnic Orientation of I & E Department, Programs, 2/17/1972 (Box 64, Folder 57)
        - Eoms, 2/17/1978-11/1978 (Box 64, Folder 58)
        - I & E Program: Objectives, Priorities, Specific Projects, March 1, 1972-June 30, 1972, 2/29/1972 (Box 64, Folder 59)
        - Eoms, 1/31/1977-12/1977 (Box 64, Folder 60)
        - Eoms, 1975-1976 (Box 64, Folder 61)
  - Filer Commission, 2/26/1975-12/11/1975 (Box 64, Folder 62)
  - Helms Amendment, No AB in Aid Programs, 11/30/1973-7/29/1974 (Box 64, Folder 63)
  - I & E Department, Elliot, Robin, Memos, Mimeos from 1971
    - 8/17/1971-1974 (Box 64, Folder 64)
    - 1975-9/19/1977 (Box 64)
  - Public Information, Elliot, Robin, Memos, Mimeos, 1/26/1978-12/4/1978 (Box 64, Folder 65)
  - I & E Department, Elliot, Robin
    - Minutes, Implication PSI Case, 7/21/1977 (Box 64, Folder 66)
    - Population Information Project Proposal, 12/6/1976 (Box 64, Folder 67)
  - Public Information Department, Elliot, R., Publicist/Personality, circa 1977 (Box 64, Folder 68)
  - I & E Department, Elliot, Robin
    - Program & Budget, 7/24/1972 (Box 64, Folder 69)
    - Proposal for Involving American Youth in World Population Year 1974, 3/7/1973 (Box 64, Folder 70)
    - Proposal on Procedures for Review of Affiliate Materials, 2/3/1972 (Box 64, Folder 71)
    - Publicity Workshops, 1/1975 (Box 64, Folder 72)
    - "St. Louis Paper" Planned Births, the Future of the Family Etc., 7/1977-8/1977 (Box 64, Folder 73)
    - I & E Department Reports, 8/25/1976-10/5/1977 (Box 64, Folder 74)
    - ZPG Projected Media Plan & Comments, 1/15/1973 (Box 64, Folder 75)
    - Teenage Program, 4/3/1972 (Box 64, Folder 76)
    - Transfer Payment to AGI, 6/22/1977 (Box 64, Folder 77)
    - Van Vleck Book, 5/14/1971-3/1/1973 (Box 64, Folder 78)
    - Chronological from July 1, 1971
      - 7/7/1971-1974 (Box 64, Folder 79)
      - 1975-1/28/1976 (Box 64)
  - Wyles, Doug, Production Radio Spots, 6/1978-1979 (Box 64, Folder 80)
  - I & E Department, Johnson, Gina
    - Correspondence & Memos
      - 7/11/1973-1974 (Box 65, Folder 1)
      - 1975-4/12/1979 (Box 65)
    - Director of Publications, Publications Memos, 3/5/1980 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - I & E Department
    - Kenney, Asta, Assistant Coordinator Public Affairs, 2/18/1977-9/19/1978 (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - Draft for Public Affairs Manual, 3/1978 (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - Medicaid Abortion Survey 1977-1978, 12/19/1977 (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - Public Information Mailings from July, 1979, 5/16/1979-9/24/1979 (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - LYDIA NEUMANN
      - Public Information Alerts, Neumann, Lydia, 1/14/1977-9/12/1979 (Box 65, Folder 7)
      - I & E Department, Neumann, Lydia, Coordinator for PA, 10/14/1976-9/20/1979 (Box 65, Folder 8)
      - Public Information, Neumann, Lydia, Public Affairs Conference Washington DC, June 10, 1979-June 12, 1979 (Box 65, Folder 9)
      - Neumann, Lydia, Public Information Fact Sheets 1977 - Draft, 9/19/1977 (Box 65, Folder 10)
      - Public Affairs, Public Impact Program, 6/18/1979 (Box 65, Folder 11)
      - Public Information Mailings, 2/1979-9/12/1979 (Box 65, Folder 12)
      - Neumann/Kenney Public Information, Monthly Public Affairs Mailings, 2/1978-10/1978 (Box 65, Folder 13)
      - Neumann/Kenney I & E Department, Monthly Public Affairs Mailing from April, 1977, 4/1977-1/1978 (Box 65, Folder 14)
  - I & E Department
    - Neumann, L., Public Affairs Memos, 1/4/1976-10/19/1979 (Box 65, Folder 15)
    - Public Affairs News Flashes, circa 1977 (Box 65, Folder 16)
  - Public Affairs, Planned Parenthood Public Affairs Contracts, 1979 (Box 65, Folder 17)
  - Public Information, Public Affairs Kit, 5/1978 (Box 65, Folder 18)
  - I & E Department, Lynn Landman
    - All News Media, 1/20/1970-6/1/1970 (Box 65, Folder 19)
    - Nelson Hearings, 1/13/1970-3/4/1970 (Box 65, Folder 20)
  - I & E Department, D. L. Millstone
    - Affiliate Correspondence, 10/3/1969-6/28/1971 (Box 65, Folder 21)
    - Criticisms & Review, 12/16/1969-5/25/1971 (Box 65, Folder 22)
    - Film Promotion, 9/25/1970 (Box 65, Folder 23)
    - General Correspondence, 3/5/1971-8/7/1972 (Box 65, Folder 24)
    - General Correspondence, 10/23/1969-10/27/1970 (Box 65, Folder 25)
    - Industry Correspondence, 11/1969 (Box 65, Folder 26)
    - Labor Unions, 3/25/1969-6/4/1970 (Box 65, Folder 27)
    - Langston Hughes, 1/1966 (Box 65, Folder 28)
    - Mental Health, 1969-2/1970 (Box 65, Folder 29)
    - Patient Recruitment, Correspondence, 1/9/1970-3/31/1970 (Box 65, Folder 30)
    - Permission to Reprint, 10/24/1969-10/12/1971 (Box 65, Folder 31)
    - Population Education, 4/20/1970-2/22/1973 (Box 65, Folder 32)
    - Population Education, Population Dynamics of Commonwealth Pennsylvania, Dept of Education, 3/23/1972 (Box 65, Folder 33)
    - Population Ed Report on Pop Ed Projects, 2/1972 (Box 65, Folder 34)
    - Printers & Publishers, Correspondence, 4/4/1969-6/29/1971 (Box 65, Folder 35)
    - Proposals for Patient Education Films, 4/22/1971 (Box 65, Folder 36)
    - Project Plans, 12/1/1969-6/3/1970 (Box 65, Folder 37)
    - Publications & Brochures, 6/1/1970-6/24/1971 (Box 65, Folder 38)
    - Publications, Report March, 4/6/1971 (Box 65, Folder 39)
    - Requests for Papers, 5/13/1970 (Box 65, Folder 40)
    - Sex Education, Correspondence, 2/27/1970-8/16/1971 (Box 65, Folder 41)
  - I & E Department, General Correspondence, Murry Salberg, 1/12/1970-12/9/1970 (Box 65, Folder 42)
  - Scanlan, John, Staff Annual Meeting Evaluations, 10/20/1970-10/27/1970 (Box 65, Folder 43)
  - I & E Department, John Scanlan
    - Memos, 1/6/1970-12/16/1970 (Box 65, Folder 44)
    - General Correspondence, 11/26/1969-6/28/1971 (Box 65, Folder 45)
    - Memos, 1/15/1971-5/20/1971 (Box 65, Folder 46)
    - Mimeos, Memos, 1/15/1970-5/28/1971 (Box 65, Folder 47)
    - Public Service Advertising Campaign, 1/13/1971 (Box 65, Folder 48)
  - I & E Department, Thanhauser, Merrie
    - Correspondence & Memos
      - 10/15/1973-1974 (Box 65, Folder 49)
      - 1975-8/10/1976 (Box 65)
    - Public Affairs, Facts of Life
      - 1973-1974 (Box 65, Folder 50)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 65)
    - Recommended Guidelines, Regional, State, Affiliate Public Affairs Relationships, n.d. (Box 65, Folder 51)
  - I & E Department, Arthur L. Young, General Correspondence, 1/15/1970-2/4/1971 (Box 65, Folder 52)
  - PRESS RELEASES
    - Communications, Press Releases, 6/4/1980 (Box 65, Folder 53)
    - Public Information, Press Releases, 1/22/1979-11/14/1979 (Box 65, Folder 54)
    - I & E Department, Press Releases, 1/22/1978-12/12/1978 (Box 65, Folder 55)
    - I & E Department, Press Releases
      - 1/14/1975-11/25/1977 (Box 65, Folder 56-58)
      - 1/20/1961-12/20/1974 (Box 66, Folder 1-14)
    - John D. Rockefeller Wins Lasker Award in PP, 10/23/1961 (Box 66, Folder 15)
    - Press Releases
      - 5/2/1954-11/17/1960 (Box 66, Folder 16-22)
  - Medical Abortion Loan & Technical Assistance Program, 3/1979 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Abortion Loan, Field Department, Stein, F.
    - Abortion Program Budget, 8/20/1976 (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - Abortion Loans to Individuals, 11/23/1976-3/27/1978 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Administration/Field Abortion Statistics, Stein, F., 12/30/1975 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Surgical Loan/Technical Assistance Medical Abortion Trust Fund, 10/24/1979 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Abortion Loan/Technical Assistance Field, Stein F., Committee on Organization, 1976 (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Abortion Loan/Technical Assistance Medical, Stein, Issue of Access to Abortion, Minutes of Board Discussion, 6/15/1978 (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Field Dept Abortion, Stein, NARHC, 5/4/1974 (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Abortion Loan, Medical Affiliates Providing Abortion Services, 12/2/1977-1/16/1978 (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - AFFILIATES
    - Abortion Loan/Technical Assistance, Medical
      - PP Association of Phoenix, AZ from 1975 (F. Stein), 3/12/1975-10/5/1976 (Box 67, Folder 10)
      - PP Association, Humboldt County, Eureka, CA (F. Stein), 2/15/1977-1/31/1980 (Box 67, Folder 11)
      - PP Association, Orange, County, CA from 1975 (F. Stein), 9/22/1975 (Box 67, Folder 12)
      - PP, Monterey County, Pacific Grove, CA from 1975 (F. Stein), 9/17/1975-10/10/1975 (Box 67, Folder 13)
      - PP Association, Sacramento, CA from 1975 (F. Stein), 8/26/1975-5/16/1979 (Box 67, Folder 14)
      - PP, San Diego County, San Diego, CA, 9/19/1975 (Box 67, Folder 15)
      - PP Alameda, San Francisco, 9/18/1975-8/31/1978 (Box 67, Folder 16)
      - PP Association, Santa Clara County, San Jose, CA, 9/9/1975-9/10/1979 (Box 67, Folder 17)
      - PP Association, San Mateo County, San Mateo, CA, 9/18/1975-10/18/1979 (Box 67, Folder 18)
      - PP of Marin County, San Rafael, CA, 4/20/1979-8/6/1979 (Box 67, Folder 19)
      - PP of Santa Barbara County, Santa Barbara, CA, 7/30/1979-10/29/1979 (Box 67, Folder 20)
      - PP of Santa Cruz County, Santa Cruz, CA, 9/17/1975 (Box 67, Folder 21)
      - PP Contra Costa County, Walnut Creek, CA, 1975 (Box 67, Folder 22)
      - PP, Hartford (Chapter PPLC), 12/7/1979 (Box 67, Folder 23)
      - PP League of Connecticut, New Haven, Conn from 1974
        - 1974 (Box 67, Folder 24)
        - 1975-3/8/1978 (Box 67)
      - Delaware League for PP, Wilmington, DE, 5/7/1976 (Box 67, Folder 25)
      - PP of Metropolitan Washington DC, 6/11/1976-5/11/1977 (Box 67, Folder 26)
      - PP Association of South Florida, Opa Locka, FL, 12/10/1976-1/16/1979 (Box 67, Folder 27)
      - PP of Atlanta Area, Atlanta, GA, 9/13/1976 (Box 67, Folder 28)
      - PP of East Central Georgia, Augusta, GA
        - 1974 (Box 67, Folder 29)
        - 1975-9/2/1976 (Box 67)
      - PP, Inc, Honolulu, HI (F. Stein), 4/19/1976-5/3/1976 (Box 67, Folder 30)
      - PP Association of Idaho, Boise, ID, 10/5/1976-1/16/1979 (Box 67, Folder 31)
      - PP Association of Chicago, IL, 11/29/1979 (Box 67, Folder 32)
      - PP of Northwest IN, Merrillville, IN from 1976 (Formerly Gary), 3/26/1976-4/14/1980 (Box 67, Folder 33)
      - PP of East Central Indiana, Muncie, IN, 3/26/1976 (Box 67, Folder 34)
      - PP of North Central Indiana, South Bend, 8/10/1976-4/19/1977 (Box 67, Folder 35)
      - PP of Iowa, Des Monies, IA, 11/27/1973 (Box 67, Folder 36)
      - PP of Kansas, Wichita, KS (F.Stein) from 1974
        - 1974 (Box 67, Folder 37)
        - 1975-2/12/1976 (Box 67)
      - PP Center, Inc. Louisville, KY (F. Stein), 8/16/1974 (Box 67, Folder 38)
      - PP Association of Maryland, Baltimore, MD (F. Stein) from 1974
        - 1974 (Box 67, Folder 39)
        - 1975-4/12/1978 (Box 67)
      - PP Washtenaw City League PP, Ann Arbor, MI (F. Stein)
        - 9/11/1973-1974 (Box 67, Folder 40)
        - 1975-3/15/1977 (Box 67)
      - PP League Inc., Detroit, MI, 1975-1979 (Box 67, Folder 41)
      - Flint Community PP Association, Flint, MI (F. Stein), 7/14/1976 (Box 67, Folder 42)
      - Reproductive Health Care Center, Kalamazoo (F. Stein), 5/11/1978-1/8/1980 (Box 67, Folder 43)
      - PP Kalamazoo - Alternatives Kalamazoo (F. Stein) from 1973
        - 9/10/1973-1974 (Box 67, Folder 44)
        - 1975-2/24/1976 (Box 67)
      - Muskegon Area PP, Inc Muskegon, MI, 9/21/1977 (Box 67, Folder 45)
      - PP Kalamazoo - Alternatives Merger, 8/22/1975-8/5/1976 (Box 67, Folder 46)
      - PP of Minnesota, Inc. St., Paul, MN (F. Stein), 12/3/1975-10/10/1977 (Box 67, Folder 47)
      - PP of Central Missouri, Columbia, Mo (F. Stein) from 1974
        - 1974 (Box 67, Folder 48)
        - 1975-2/21/1980 (Box 67)
      - PP of Western Missouri/Kansas, Kansas City from 1973
        - 10/9/1973-1974 (Box 67, Folder 49)
        - 1975 (Box 67)
      - PP of Northern Nevada, Reno, Nevada, 6/9/1978 (Box 67, Folder 50)
      - PP of Hudson County, Hudson Health Center Bergen Health Center Jersey City, NJ
        - 1974 (Box 67, Folder 51)
        - 1975 (Box 67)
      - PP of Monmouth County, Shrewsbury, NJ, 1/3/1977-11/20/1978 (Box 67, Folder 52)
      - PP Association of Albany, Albany, NY, 8/16/1976-9/24/1976 (Box 67, Folder 53)
      - PP of East Suffolk, Patchogue, NY, 2/4/1975-9/8/1975 (Box 67, Folder 54)
      - PP of Dutchess - Ulster, Poughkeepsie, NY, 2/4/1977 (Box 67, Folder 55)
      - PP of Schenectady & Affiliate Counties, NY, 3/16/1977-12/24/1979 (Box 67, Folder 56)
      - PP Center of Syracuse, Inc. NY, 11/8/1978 (Box 67, Folder 57)
      - PP of Rockland County, West Nyack, NY, 7/1/1975-7/17/1978 (Box 67, Folder 58)
      - PP of Westchester, White Plains, NY, 9/24/1976-11/3/1977 (Box 67, Folder 59)
      - Triangle Area, Chapel Hill, NC, 6/15/1977 (Box 67, Folder 60)
      - PP Association of Greater Charlotte, Charlotte, NC from 1974
        - 1974 (Box 67, Folder 61)
        - 1975-4/19/1979 (Box 67)
      - PP Association of Summit County, Inc Akron, OH, 12/24/1979 (Box 67, Folder 62)
      - PP Association of Cincinnati, OH from 1973
        - 11/27/1973-1974 (Box 67, Folder 63)
        - 1975 (Box 67)
      - PP of Central Ohio, Columbus, OH, 6/30/1975-1/8/1980 (Box 67, Folder 64)
      - PP of Miami Valley, Dayton, OH, 3/6/1978-6/8/1978 (Box 67, Folder 65)
      - PP Association Bucks County, Bristol, PA, 1/6/1977 (Box 67, Folder 66)
      - PP Association Southeastern PA, Philadelphia, 1/17/1975-10/15/1976 (Box 67, Folder 67)
      - PP Center of Pittsburgh, Pittsburgh, PA, 1/17/1975-10/15/1976 (Box 67, Folder 68)
      - PP Central Pennsylvania, York, PA, 5/9/1977-5/11/1977 (Box 67, Folder 69)
      - PP of Rhode Island, Providence, RI from 1974
        - 1974 (Box 67, Folder 70)
        - 1975-3/7/1979 (Box 67)
      - PP Central South Carolina, Columbia, 9/13/1978-11/27/1978 (Box 67, Folder 71)
      - PP Association Knox County, Knoxville, TN from 1974
        - 5/31/1974 (Box 67, Folder 72)
        - 1975-8/26/1976 (Box 67)
      - Memphis PP Association, Inc, Memphis, TN from 1973
        - 5/30/1973-1974 (Box 67, Folder 73)
        - 1975-12/13/1978 (Box 67)
      - PP Association of Nashville,TN (F. Stein), 8/26/1976-8/31/1978 (Box 67, Folder 74)
      - Pemian Basin PP Inc. Odessa, TX, 3/4/1977 (Box 67, Folder 75)
      - PP Association of Utah, Salt Lake City, UT, 4/10/1975 (Box 67, Folder 76)
      - PP Association of Vermont, Burlington, VT from 1974
        - 1974 (Box 67, Folder 77)
        - 1975-6/13/1978 (Box 67)
  - BANKS
    - Stein, F., Citibank, 2/8/1977-10/10/1979 (Box 67, Folder 78)
    - Abortion Loan Fund, First National City Bank from 1973
      - 5/8/1973-1974 (Box 67, Folder 79)
      - 1975-12/28/1976 (Box 67)
    - Stein, F., FNCR Revolving Credit Agreement, 10/5/1973 (Box 67, Folder 80)
    - Justice Campaign/ Consumer Loan Funds
      - Legal (Paul, Eve), 4/4/1979-4/18/1979 (Box 67, Folder 81)
      - Affiliate Applicants, 6/7/1978-12/7/1979 (Box 67, Folder 82)
      - Roff, E., 4/2/1979-2/21/1980 (Box 67, Folder 83)
      - Stein, F., 4/7/1978-3/29/1979 (Box 67, Folder 84)
      - PP Northern Arizona, Phoenix, AZ Surgical Services Loan/Tech, 6/19/1978-1/23/1980 (Box 67, Folder 85)
      - PP of San Diego County, San Diego, CA, 6/22/1978 (Box 67, Folder 86)
      - PP Contra Costa County, Walnut Creek, CA, 6/20/1978-4/30/1979 (Box 67, Folder 87)
      - PP League of Connecticut, New Haven, CT, 3/29/1978-9/21/1978 (Box 67, Folder 88)
      - PP of Metropolitan Washington DC, 5/8/1979-8/6/1979 (Box 67, Folder 89)
      - PP Southwest Florida, Sarasota, FL, 6/15/1978-4/11/1979 (Box 67, Folder 90)
      - PP Palm Beach Area, West Palm Beach, FL, 1/20/1978-1/22/1980 (Box 67, Folder 91)
      - PP of East Central Georgia, Augusta, GA, 5/1/1979-11/1/1979 (Box 67, Folder 92)
      - PP of Idaho Boise, ID, 11/29/1979-12/10/1979 (Box 67, Folder 93)
      - PP Springfield Area, Springfield, IL, 4/26/1979-5/9/1979 (Box 67, Folder 94)
      - PP South Central Indiana, Bloomington, IN, 6/20/1978-4/11/1979 (Box 67, Folder 95)
      - PP Association of Indianapolis, IN, 4/30/1979-1/23/1980 (Box 67, Folder 96)
      - PP of Northwest Indiana, Gary, IN, 6/23/1978-11/8/1978 (Box 67, Folder 97)
      - PP of Iowa, Des Monies, IA, 4/30/1979-11/1/1979 (Box 67, Folder 98)
      - PP of Sioux City, IA, 6/19/1978-10/26/1979 (Box 67, Folder 99)
      - PP of Kansas, Inc, Wichita, KS, 4/30/1979-11/1/1979 (Box 67, Folder 100)
      - PP Center, Inc. Louisville, KY, 6/20/1978-3/20/1979 (Box 67, Folder 101)
      - PP of Western Missouri/Kansas Kansas City, MO, 6/20/1978-4/11/1979 (Box 67, Folder 102)
      - PP of Central Missouri, Columbia, MO, 1979 (Box 67, Folder 103)
      - PP Association of St.Louis, Mo, 4/27/1979-9/19/1979 (Box 67, Folder 104)
      - PP of Missoula County, Missoula, MT, 6/12/1978-4/11/1979 (Box 67, Folder 105)
      - PP of Omaha, Council Bluffs, Omaha, NE, 6/19/1978-8/8/1979 (Box 67, Folder 106)
      - PP of Southern Nevada, Las Vegas, NV, 6/12/1978-1/23/1980 (Box 67, Folder 107)
      - PP of Northern Nevada, Reno, NV, 6/16/1978-1/23/1980 (Box 67, Folder 108)
      - PP Greater Camden Area, Camden, NJ, 4/27/1979-1/23/1980 (Box 67, Folder 109)
      - Justice Campaign/Consumer Loan Fund of Northwest New Jersey, Morristown, NJ, 6/22/1978-6/12/1979 (Box 67, Folder 110)
      - Bernalillo County PP Association Albuquerque, 6/22/1978-8/13/1979 (Box 67, Folder 111)
      - PP of Greater Charlotte - Charlotte, NC, 5/18/1978-7/11/1978 (Box 67, Folder 112)